{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "Mum, _______ you possibly let me have a couple of pounds?",
            "a": "might ",
            "b": "should",
            "c": "could ",
            "d": "may",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think we _______ tell the children?",
            "a": "should ",
            "b": "ought",
            "c": "might ",
            "d": "may",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother _______ come next week, but I am still not sure.",
            "a": "would ",
            "b": "ought",
            "c": "might ",
            "d": "can",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven't decided yet, but we _______ go to Greece next year.",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "can",
            "c": "should ",
            "d": "ought",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You _______ to come as early as possible.",
            "a": "should ",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "ought ",
            "d": "must",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I got married, I ________ cook.",
            "a": "wasn't ",
            "b": "couldn't",
            "c": "didn't know ",
            "d": "can't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "_______ I come in Mr Green, or am I bothering you?",
            "a": "Must ",
            "b": "May",
            "c": "Mustn't ",
            "d": "Couldn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shall I do the shopping today?' 'No,_______ you do it today. It can wait.'",
            "a": "musn't ",
            "b": "oughtn't",
            "c": "can't ",
            "d": "needn't",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are you going to hang the picture?' 'I don't know, I _______ hang it here.'",
            "a": "mightn't ",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "oughtn't ",
            "d": "should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Freddie, _______ your father speak French?' 'No, he can't.'",
            "a": "could ",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "should ",
            "d": "can",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "11",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}